m -164 21 l -51 -26 l 3 -48 l 95 -79 l 183 -111 l 192 4 l 66 43 l -44 83 l -159 116 l -162 73 l -164 41
Nakatomi Plaza
I could have got through anytime
Cold lonely puritan
What are you fighting for?
It's not my security
It's just an old war
Not even a cold war
Don't say it in Russian
Don't say it in German
Just say it in broken English
Lose your father your husband
Your mother your children
What are you fighting for?
It's not my reality
It's just an old war
Not even a cold war
Don't say it in Russian
Don't say it in German
Just say it in broken English
The Devil's Stocking (doo doo bee doo)...
Soldiers march down the street in ranks
to wage war on a distant enemy
In a time gone mad,
they keep on walking, just to die
The Devil's Stocking (doo doo bee doo)...
Who knows what is at work
deep down in their hearts?
It's too dark in there to see anything
Standing in a windswept field
counting up the number of bodies
The soldiers in the square
dance around in a circle
But they don't have time to do so
Not if they're going to make their escape
Not if they're going to prolong their lives
From a clock tower at the end of the world
a rotten shadow watches
as they fall upon the crimson field,
with arms folded, folded, folded
(arms folded, folded folded)
and laughs
The Devil's Stocking (doo doo bee doo)...
Soldiers march down the street in ranks
to wage war on a distant enemy
In a time gone mad,
they keep on walking, just to die
They keep on walking... They keep on walking...